//create question
let questions = [

    {
        question: "2 + 2 = ?",

        choiceA: "4",

        choiceB: "6",

        choiceC: "d",

        choiceD: "8",

        correct: "A",

    }, {

        question: "10 + 19 = ?",

        choiceA: "29",

        choiceB: "17",

        choiceC: "7",

        choiceD: "None of the above",

        correct: "C",

    }, {

        question: "17 * 1 = ?",

        choiceA: "g",

        choiceB: "k",

        choiceC: "q",

        choiceD: "x",

        correct: "C",

    }, {

        question: "2 * 2 = ?",

        choiceA: "g",

        choiceB: "d",

        choiceC: "4",

        choiceD: "22",

        correct: "B"

    }, {

        question: "4 + xy = ?",

        choiceA: "8xy",

        choiceB: "4boys",

        choiceC: "4xy",

        choiceD: "5-xy",

        correct: "C"

    }, {

        question: "x + yz = ?",

        choiceA: "eyz",

        choiceB: "xyz",

        choiceC: "abc",

        choiceD: "123",

        correct: "A",

    }, {

        question: "11 + 11 = ?",

        choiceA: "9",

        choiceB: "6",

        choiceC: "4",

        choiceD: "22",

        correct: "C",

    }, {

        question: "abc is easy as = ?",

        choiceA: "69",

        choiceB: "do re mi",

        choiceC: "407",

        choiceD: "123",

        correct: "D",

    }, {

        question: "123xyz + abc = ?",

        choiceA: "abc123xyz",

        choiceB: "123abcxyz",

        choiceC: "123xyzabc",

        choiceD: "all of the above",

        correct: "B"

    }, {

        question: "3 * 3 = ?",

        choiceA: "9",

        choiceB: "6",

        choiceC: "i",

        choiceD: "n",

        correct: "C",

    }, {

        question: "5 * 2 = ?",

        choiceA: "10",

        choiceB: "g",

        choiceC: "4",

        choiceD: "j",

        correct: "D"

    },
    {

        question: "44 + 0 = ?",

        choiceA: "h",

        choiceB: "220",

        choiceC: "8",

        choiceD: "none of the above",

        correct: "C",

    }, {

        question: "99 * 1 = ?",

        choiceA: "9",

        choiceB: "99",

        choiceC: "i",

        choiceD: "100",

        correct: "C"

    }

];
